宝贝儿 找我什么事
Honeydew! What's up?
猜猜谁来了
Guess who's here.
是你爸
Your dad!
他从可可海滩一路开着房车过来的
He drove his R.V. all the way up from Cocoa Beach.
儿子啊 在努力工作吗
Hey, Son, working hard?
他会说 工作个屁
He's gonna say "Hardly working."
我原本是打算告诉你他出发的事
I meant to tell you he was driving out.
-他说了吗 -说了
- Did he say it? - Oh, yeah.
好孩子
Good kid.
他本该过几天才到的
He wasn't supposed to show up for a few more days.
猜猜他给我们带了什么来
Well, guess what he brought us.
一只狗 给我们养的
A dog... to keep.
没错 没错
Yes! Yes.
没错 我早该把狗的事告诉克莱尔
Yes, I should have told Claire about the dog,
我本来准备说的
and I was going to.
我只是想等她心情好时再说
But I was just waiting for her to be in the right mood.
其实 几天前的某晚她心情就挺好
Actually, I did get one right mood a couple nights ago,
可我用那晚"干"了其他的事
but I cashed that in for something else.
-我是不是有大麻烦了 -非常非常大
- Am I in trouble? - Oh, really, really big.
你吓到我了 到底有多糟
Okay, I'm a little scared. How bad is this?
我们家立了新规矩 不许进卧室
Oh, well we have a new rule- no sleeping in the bedroom.
普里契特先生 我是本 本·杜根
Mr. Pritchett. Uh, Ben- Ben Dugan.
我是米奇的高中同学
I went to high school with Mitch.
我们一起参加过戏剧社
We were in the drama club together.
-想起来了 -是的
- That's right. - Yeah.
老天 你卸了老头子妆
Geez, I didn't recognize you
我都认不出你了
without that old-guy makeup on.
你和米奇演的《阳光小子》火爆全场
You know, you and Mitch knocked The Sunshine Boys out of the park.
米奇演得很棒
Mitch was really great in that.
我一直觉得他是当演员的料
I always thought he should be an actor.
他现在找了份真正的工作
Yeah, he's got a real job now.
他做了律师 你呢
He's a lawyer. How about you?
-我还在演戏 -那敢情好
- Still acting. - Fantastic.
其实挺过瘾的 我演了部新电影
Actually, it's exciting. I'm in a new movie,
《枫叶大道》 刚上映的
Maple Drive. Just came out.
真的吗 哇 我认识名人了
You're kidding me. Look at me. I know somebody famous.
那我先走了
Uh, anyway, I got to go.
-见到你真高兴 -我也是
- Great to see you. - Good to see you too.
这孩子成电影明星了
Kid's a movie star.
-医生怎么说 -没有蛀牙
- Hey, how'd it go in there? - No cavities.
我还得了把免费牙刷
And I got a free toothbrush.
嘿 你想去看电影吗
Hey, you want to go to the movies?
我刚听说一部好片子
I just heard about a good one.
可我该去上学了
But I'm supposed to be in school.
你还应该用牙线呢
Well, you're supposed to floss too,
你不也躲过了吗
but you got away with that one.
来 走吧
Come on. Let's go.
我生命中最美好的几个日子之一
One of the greatest days of my life...
就是我老爹带我逃课
was when my old man sprung me from school
然后带我去坐卡车
and took me to the track.
我想让曼尼有同样的体验
I wanted to do the same type of thing for Manny,
再说如果歌洛莉亚听到这事
plus I figured when Gloria heard about it,
也许会在卧室好好犒赏我
maybe it pays off in the bedroom.
我老爹当年莫非也是为了这个
I wonder if that's why my old man did it.
靠 毁了
Oh, crap.
你婆婆非要养这只狗
Your mother-in-law just had to have the dog.
结果发现原来她对狗过敏
Turns out she's allergic.
宠物店就没个宽限期
And the pet store didn't have a grace period
或者包退换之类的吗
or a return policy or anything?
它是从宠物收留所领回来的
I got him from the pound.
堪萨斯州刮龙卷风了吧
Was there a twister in Kansas?
不然怎么把房子刮到我家车道上了
'Cause there's a house in my driveway.
欢迎回家 邓菲先生
Welcome home, Mr. Dunphy.
很高兴见到你 邓菲先生
Uh, always a pleasure, Mr. Dunphy.
我也是 邓菲先生 请把它放在那里
Indeed it is, Mr. Dunphy. Place it there.
-好的好的 -真怀念啊 来抱一个
- Oh, I shall. I shall. - I miss this. Get in here.
我爸超级棒
My dad is awesome.
他特别好 永远积极向上 笑口常开
He's awesome. He's always up. He's always happy.
他跟我是好哥们
I mean, he and I are best buds.
我们就像一个模子刻出来的
We're like two peas in a pod.
或者是连体双胞胎 或者双头蛇
Or Siamese twins. Or a snake with two heads.
-他们在万圣节扮过以上所有角色 -没错
- They've actually been all those things for Halloween. - Yeah.
哎哟 这一定是斯科特吧
Oy. This must be Scout, huh?
我得警告你 他会脱毛
I should warn you. He sheds.
我一路上让他上床和我一起睡
I made the mistake of letting him sleep with me on the road.
我那床单就跟被俩野人滚过一样
Now my sheets look like two bigfoots did it.
原谅我的粗俗用语
Pardon the language.
-我妈好吗 -说到那个"大脚野人"
- How's Mom? - Speaking of big feet, eh?
她和她的闺蜜们乘游轮旅游去了
She's on a cruise with her girlfriends,
大多都是恐龙 也有几个尚有几分姿色
some of which are not totally unattractive.
那倒提醒了我 她给孩子们带了礼物
Oh, that reminds me. She sent some gifts for the kids.
我马上就回来
Um, I will be right back.
-你们仨先套套近乎 -没问题
- You three get better acquainted. - Will do!
-慢走 -没问题
- Bye! - Will do!
真不敢相信你没和我商量就领来了只狗
I cannot believe you got a dog without consulting me.
此事需要全家共同商议才行
This was a major family decision.
-我错了 -知道就好
- It was wrong. - Yeah.
对不起
And I'm sorry.
可我们早就讨论过养狗的事了
But we have talked about getting a dog for years,
全家只有你不同意
and you're the only one who wasn't into it.
因为我知道照顾它都会是我的活儿
Because I knew that I would be the one taking care of it.
不会的
That's not true.
我们都会帮忙的
No, we will all help.
这也是教导孩子责任感的大好机会
This is a great chance to teach the kids responsibility.
当年你让卢克送报纸时也是这么说的
That is exactly what you said about Luke's paper route.
有人吗
Hello?
里面有人吗
Is anyone in there?
你真适合红色
Red's a good color on you.
只是电影罢了
It's just a movie.
-它好可爱啊 -瞧它那小脸
- Oh, he's so cute. - Look at his little face.
我一直想养狗来着 谢谢爷爷
I always wanted a dog. Thanks, Grandpa.
你们要记得 养狗可是个大责任
Okay, but remember, having a dog is a major responsibility.
家里每个人都得负责任
Everyone in the family has to pitch in.
-没问题 邓太太 -没包括你 迪兰
- Can do, Mrs. D. - Not you, Dylan.
松了一口气 我最近正好忙着呢
Oh, phew. 'Cause I got a lot on my plate right now.
看看谁来了 小卡舅夫
Hey, look who's here. Uncle Cam.
嘿 我们听说来了新成员
Hey, we heard about the new addition
所以一定得来看看
and we had to come right over.
卡梅隆 又见到你了
Cameron, so good to see you again.
这衬衣真好看
Now that is a shirt.
谢了 弗兰克 我网购的
Oh, well, thank you, Frank. I get 'em online.
回头发给你链接
I'll send you a link.
好吧 我自家熏制了香肠
Oh, well, at home, I smoke sausages.
回头也给你发一节
I'll send you a link.
真经典
Classic.
-这就是莉莉吧 -是的
- And this must be Lily. - Oh, yes.
她等不及要来看新狗狗了
She just couldn't wait to meet the new doggy.
我看她待在这里挺好
I think she's good right here.
快让我来和狗狗亲热亲热
Let me get in there and get some of that doggyness.
-宝贝儿啊 -海莉
- Oh, there it is. - Haley.
-乖乖啊 -我得走了
- There it is. - I gotta go.
-怎么了 -是布莱恩 他要退出乐队
- What's wrong? - That was Brian. He just quit the band.
什么 为什么啊
What? Why?
他要搬去波特兰了
He's moving to Portland.
他父母复合了
His parents got back together.
-真可恶 -我知道
- Oh, that sucks. - I know.
我们明天的演出得取消了
Now we're gonna have to cancel the gig tomorrow.
搞不好你能找到其他的鼓手呢
Maybe you can find another drummer.
不 我想现在已经来不及找了
No. I think it's too late for that now.
我会打鼓
I play drums.
虽然自从有了莉莉以后 我许久没练了
Well, I mean, I haven't played in a while, since Lily's come along,
不过如果你紧缺人手 我就是你的人手
but if you're in a jam, I can jam.
我很高兴 可我不确定
Well, I totally would, but I'm not sure
我们玩的是同一卦的音乐
we like the same sorts of music, you know?
干嘛 我是基佬
What, because I'm gay,
就只会演奏舞台剧的音乐吗
I'm just gonna want to play show tunes?
不 因为你年纪比较大
No, because you're old.
你这话更伤人 迪兰
Wow. That hurt more, Dylan.
让他试试吧 总比取消好
Give him a chance. It's better than canceling.
你说得对 我不想白白浪费
You're right. I don't want to lose
造雾机的押金
the deposit on that fog machine.
好吧 我们试一试
Okay. Let's do it.
我以前是音乐老师
I used to be a music teacher,
但有了莉莉后我就放弃了事业
but I gave that up as soon as Lily came along.
是的 我们觉得必须有一人
Yes. Well, we just felt that it was really important...
留在家里照顾她 所以
that one of us stayed hometo raise her, so-
不是说别人的选择不好
Yeah, and that's not a judgmenton other people's choices.
只是我们的家庭观念非常传统而已
It's just that we happen to be a very traditional family.
是的 那个帮莉莉房间祈福的
Yes, that's what the disabled lesbian shaman
残疾拉拉神婆也这么说
who blessed Lily's room said too.
你还好吗 孩子
How you doin', buddy?
放轻松
All right, relax.
天啊
Oh, geez.
我跟你说 菲尔 你爸真哭了
I am telling you, Phil, the man was crying.
不可能
That is impossible.
我爹是全世界最乐天的人
My dad is the happiest guy on earth.
大概是听起来像哭吧
It probably just sounded like he was crying.
你听过他从椅子上起身的声响吗
Have you heard the noise he makes when he gets out of a chair?
不 我听得清清楚楚
No. I know what I heard.
我想大概是和你妈有关
I think this has something to do with your mom.
-什么 -想想看 他是一个人来的
- What? - Yeah, he came here alone. Think about it.
她坐游轮玩去了
She's on a cruise.
他们从没分开旅行过 所以
Yeah, and they never take separate vacations, so-
不 不可能 如果真有事
No. No, if something was wrong,
我爸会告诉我的
my dad would tell me about it.
不 菲尔 他不会说的
No, Phil, he wouldn't,
因为你们从来就没认真聊过
because you guys never actually talk about anything.
我们常聊呢
We talk all the time.
我上班时他一周打三次骚扰电话来
He crank calls me at work, like, three times a week.
-骚扰电话不算数 -但是算有趣
- Crank calls don't count. - Counts for fun.
说真的 我想你应该
No, honestly, I think that you should
搞清楚你爸到底怎么了
find out what's going on with your dad.
我爸什么事都没有
It's going to be nothing.
他又不像你爸
My dad isn't like your dad.
他没那些城府 心机之类的
There's nothing deep and dark inside.
他甜美外表下隐藏的是更多的甜美
His hard candy shell is just hiding more candy.
他应该是想出去 好孩子
I think he wants to go out. Good boy.
-聪明的狗狗 -不想扫你的兴
- Smart dog. - I hate to break it to you,
不过这招所有狗都会吧
but I think all dogs can do that.
我要出去玩
I'm gonna play outside.
怎么回事啊
What happened?
好
Okay.
我是不是先露一小手
Should I just play a little something?
好啊 不过如果打不好
Yeah. But, you know, if it doesn't work out,
你也别难过
don't feel bad.
但愿打鼓就像骑自行车一样
Well, hopefully this is- this is like riding a bicycle,
学了就永远忘不掉
and it'll all come back to me.
这是重音鼓
That's the loud one.
好吧 开始了
So... here we go.
哎呀 我真傻
Oh, silly me.
我把鼓槌给拿反了
I had the sticks in the wrong hands.
老兄 你该给鼓槌贴好左右标签
Dude, you should label those sticks.
这是警报吗 我们家被入侵了吗
Is that the alarm? Has our perimeter been breached?
不是警报 是门铃停不下来了
It's not the alarm. The doorbell won't stop ringing.
-也许是魔鬼在按门铃 -才没有魔鬼
- Maybe a demon is ringing it. - Not a demon.
谁老是在按门铃啊
Who keeps ringing the doorbell?
-肯定是魔鬼在按 -是吗
- We're pretty sure it's a demon. - Oh, yeah?
现在呢
There.
如果是魔鬼 它就会继续响了
If it were a demon, it would keep on ringing.
除非他已经进屋了 我要去武装起来
Not if he's already inside. I'm getting a weapon.
你脑子里想什么呢
What were you thinking?
带这么小的孩子去看恐怖片
Who takes a little boy to a horror movie?
你疯了吗 杰
That's loco, Jay.
有什么大不了的 你知道什么才恐怖吗
This is no big deal. You want scary?
我像他这么大时
When I was his age,
可是经历过古巴导弹危机的
I lived through the Cuban Missile Crisis.
我睡觉时都藏把黄油刀在枕头下
I slept with a butter knife under my pillow...
以防要和苏联上校搏斗
in case I had to fight some Soviet colonel.
苏联上校抓你个小屁孩干什么
Why would they send a Soviet colonel to get a little boy?
因为我能认出苏共的每一架飞机
Because I could identify every commie plane.
我们这是在说什么呢
What are we talking about?
我的意思是 恐惧也是成长的一部分
Look, all I'm saying, being scared is part of growing up.
曼尼会没事的 那有助于培养个性
Manny will get over this. It builds character.
我站第一班岗
I'll take the first watch.
你们俩最好先去睡一下
You two might as well get some rest.
长夜漫漫啊
It's gonna be a long night.
有个性吧
Character.
爸
Dad?
进来吧 门没锁
Come on in! It's open!
别说你是上隔壁借白糖来了
Don't tell me. You need a cup of sugar.
不 我只是
Nah. Just, uh-
我只是觉得 那个
I was just wondering, I don't know, uh-
您脑子里没在烦恼什么事吧
Anything on the old noodle?
除了这顶烂假发吗
Other than a bad toupee?
我开玩笑的 这可是真头发
I'm kidding, of course. This is my real hair.
-好吧 -等一下
- Well, okay. - Wait a minute.
我有事问你
I want to ask you something.
我把狗带来是不是让你为难了
Am I putting you in a bad position with this whole dog thing?
克莱尔看起来不太高兴
Claire seemed a little put out.
别理她 克莱尔一开始还不喜欢我呢
Oh, don't worry about it. Claire didn't like me at first either.
那也不怪她 解散
I can't blame her. Dismissed!
爸 你知道吗 我...
Oh, Dad, um, you know what? I, uh-
克莱尔撞见了一件事
Claire saw something,
要是我不问你 她非灭了我
and she'd kill me if I- if I didn't ask.
什么事
What is it?
你吃早饭时就不能穿条裤子吗 真叫人"哭"笑不得
Would you wear pants to breakfast, for crying out loud?
-又被你骗到了 正中弱点 -很好
- You got me again. Right in the funny bone. - All right.
拜托 斯科特 松口
Come on, Scout. Let go of it.
别 别
No, no, no!
坏狗狗 你看这个
Dog. Look at this.
他怎么会有你的胸罩
How did he get ahold of your bra?
我们出去约会
Well, uh, we were out on a date,
他有辆特别好的车 于是
and he has a really nice car, so-
你以为呢 当然是从洗衣篮里找到的
How do you think? He got it out of the laundry basket.
对这狗一秒钟也不能大意
Can't take my eyes off that dog for a second.
干嘛不把它关笼子里
Why don't you just keep him in the crate?
我关了 他自己会开笼子
I tried that. He figured out how to get out.
你不是去找你爸谈话了吗
I thought you were dealing with your dad.
没错 我们谈了 他没事
Oh, yeah, I did. He's fine, so-
你们才谈两分钟就谈好了吗
You got that from a two-minute conversation?
我直接问他还好吗
I... asked him point-blank if he was okay.
他说很好 所以我就
He said he was. So I just-
结果你们扯了几个笑话 就谈完了
Just swapped some jokes and moved on.
菲尔 你得更深入地问他
Phil, the man needs more of a push than that.
如果他想谈 他会主动说的
Look, if he wants to talk to me about it, he will.
有人的内裤搅成一团了
Geez, someone's panties are in a bunch.
-我只想表示一下关心 -不 你看
- I thought I was showing concern and- - No. Right there.
我的天 这该死的狗
Oh, my God! That damn dog!
二位 帮帮忙啊
Guys, little help?
我要上厕所了 我可不想尿裤子
I have to go to the bathroom, and I'm not gonna do it in here.
-我买了中餐外卖 -太好了 正饿着呢
- Hey, I got Chinese. - Sweet! I'm starving.
有客人呀
Oh, we have guests.
我们正合奏呢
Yeah. We're just having a little jam session.
迪兰你认识的 那边是克雷格和尼尔
You know Dylan. This is Craig. This is Neil.
我会记得他是抱着我女儿的陌生人
I'll always remember him as the stranger holding my baby.
你能到厨房来一下吗
Can I talk to you in the kitchen for a second?
好的 各位 我们休息一下
Yeah. Hey, guys, let's, uh- let's just take five.
这支龙虎少年队怎么了
What's up with 21 Jump Street?
他们的鼓手退团了
Oh, well, their drummer quit
我明晚帮他们顶替一下
and I'm gonna fill in for him tomorrow night.
不 明天我们得去胡娇家的
No, no. We have Pepper's
滑雪风情奶酪火锅派对 小卡
apres-ski fondue party tomorrow night, Cam.
不是吧
Oh, no.
你得通知乐队
So you'll just have to tell your band
另请高明了
that they're gonna have to find someone else.
不 我不能失信于他们
You know what? No. I'm not gonna let these fellas down.
我答应他们了
I made a commitment.
你也答应了胡娇 好吗
You made two commitments, okay?
而你又知道胡娇那脾气
And you know how Pepper is.
凡事必须完美
Everything has to be perfect.
你不穿厚毛衣他都能跟你急
He gets mad if you don't wear a big sweater.
我记得 去年我热得要命
Yeah, I remember. I got so hot last year,
差点晕死在奶酪上
I almost went face down in the gruyere.
所以你是想让我一个人去吗
So I'm going by myself, is that what you're saying?
我真心需要参加这个
I just feel like I kind of need this.
为了丰富你大学申请书吗
To round out your college applications?
我总是呆在家里守着莉莉
It's just that because I'm always home with Lily...
我闷得有点发疯了
I just feel like I'm going a little bit stir-crazy.
你看看那书房
Look at the den.
被我翻来覆去地粉刷
Every time I finish painting it, I start all over again.
都快赶上金门大桥了
It's like the Golden Gate Bridge.
我要回去练习了
I'm gonna go back to jamming.
得 我们必须解决这事了
Yeah, we gotta fix this.
穿厚毛衣来听演唱会
Hey, what's with the big sweater at a concert?
是基友们的穿衣风格吗
Is that a gay thing?
不 是为了胡娇的滑雪风格风奶酪火锅
No, Dad. It's for my friend Pepper's apres-ski fondue-
好吧 的确是基友们的风格
Yeah. Yeah, it's a gay thing.
最好赶紧开始
Hope they start soon.
斯科特不喜欢独守空屋
I don't think Scout likes to be left alone.
你挺喜欢那狗的嘛
You love the dog.
不 不是喜欢它 我是心疼我的沙发
No, I don't love the dog. I love my couch.
那狗看沙发的眼神就跟那是巨型香肠一样
And the dog was looking at it like it was a giant sausage.
孩子们 好消息 你的车道要腾空了
Good news, you two. You're getting your driveway back.
-明天一早我就上路 -这么快
- I'm hitting the open road in the morning. - Oh, already?
-没错 -迫不急待想回家看妈了吧
- Yeah. - Anxious to get home and see Mom, huh?
不 我打算要随风游荡一下
No, I'm just gonna drive wherever the wind blows me,
一般也就是飘到隔壁的车道
which is usually into the next lane.
我们去喝苏打汽水好吗 爷爷
Can we get some sodas, Grandpa?
好呀 不过只能一杯 我还得开车
Okay, but just one. I'm driving. Come on.
他居然不回家 他从没离开我妈
He's not going home? He's never been away from my mom
超过看医生的时间
for longer than a doctor's appointment.
亲爱的 我知道 我就说嘛
Honey, I know. I told you.
我一直很同情那些
I always felt bad for people
和父亲关系疏远的人
with emotionally distant fathers.
结果我也是其中之一
It turns out I'm one of 'em.
我没沦落成脱衣舞男真是奇迹
It's a miracle I didn't end up a stripper.
谢谢各位来观看演出
Thanks, everybody, for coming out.
下面是我们写的几首歌
These are some songs we wrote.
一二 一二三
One, two. One, two, three.
*宝贝别走 我只想让你知道*
* Baby, don't leave me I just want you to know *
*我只想让你知道*
* I want you to know *
*有些热情我自己也控制不了*
* There's something inside me that I cannot control *
*我控制不了*
* I cannot control *
-我俩的男朋友都帅呆了 -没错
- Our boyfriends totally rock! - I know, right?
*听到你高喊我的名字 我就彻底疯狂*
* I heard you screamin' my name I'm goin' insane *
我原计划
Well, the plan was...
看十分钟的演出
to watch him for 10 minutes
就溜去胡娇的派对
and then run out to Pepper's party.
*奔腾在我的血管中*
* Coursing through my veins *
可他在台上太亮眼了
But he was so great up there.
我怎么舍得离开
How-How could I leave?
*别害怕*
* But don't be afraid *
*我就是你的吸血鬼*
* I'll be your vampire *
那是他的光辉时刻
It was his moment.
棒吧
I know!
那时刻持续了很久很久的时间
And his moment went on for a really, really long time.
久到我可以溜去参加派对
Turns out I could have run to the party
再回来听他的最后一敲
and made it back for the end of his moment.
曼尼 去刷牙准备上床睡觉
Manny, go brush your teeth and get ready for bed, okay?
-上你的床 -我能看电视吗
- Your bed. - Can I watch TV?
-只能看十分钟哦 -好
- Mmm, only 10 minutes. - Okay.
你好 杰 我是本·杜根
Hey, Jay, it's Ben Dugan.
我收到你的留言了
I got your message.
我很乐意帮忙 我晚上来拜访
Uh, yes, I'm happy to help out. I'll swing by tonight.
-谁啊 -是本
- What's that? - That's Ben.
演电影的那个
That's the guy who was in the movie.
我想如果曼尼看到他真人很善良
I figure when Manny sees him, sees how nice he is,
他会发现电影都是假的
he'll realize it's all pretend.
-你觉得会有效吗 -那家伙人可好了
- You think that will work? - Guy's a sweetheart.
曼尼和他聊一聊
Manny's gonna spend two minutes with him.
听他解释电影拍摄过程
He'll explain how the movie's made.
他还带了他的道具刀来
He's even bringing his fake machete.
橡胶做的
Thing's made of rubber.
你是曼尼吧 我是来找你的
Hey, are you Manny? I'm here for you.
瞧我带了什么
Look what I got.
妈 他来了
Mom, he's here!
怎么啦 怎么啦
Que paso? Que paso? Que paso?
我们得换张大床了
We're gonna need a bigger bed!
靠
Oh, geez.
天啊 真的是他
Oh, my God! I think that's him.
-你没溜走啊 -没有
- You stayed. - Yeah.
我可是乐队家属
Well, you know, I'm-I'm with the band.
我觉得演出某些地方还需改进
I thought the gig was a little sloppy in spots,
不过等我学会了所有的歌
but I think once I learn all the songs-
我以为你只参加这一次呢
I thought- I thought this was a one-time thing?
你开玩笑吧 我们秒杀了全场
Are you kidding? We destroyed in there.
你没听到有个妹子大喊我的名字吗
Did you hear that one lady screaming my name?
那是菲尔喊的 他喝了罐红牛
That was Phil. He had a Red Bull.
各位 表现得不错吧
Hey, guys. Good gig, huh?
-是啊 棒极了 -震撼的演出
- Yeah. Totally awesome, man. - Heck of a gig.
大伙儿好啊
Hey, guys.
嘿 你不是去波特兰了吗
Hey. I thought you were in Portland.
没 我爸妈又闹崩了
No. My parents broke up again.
我不搬走了 我可以继续参加乐队了
I'm not moving. I can stay in the band.
这下可尴尬了
Well, this is awkward.
小卡
Cam.
原来是我尴尬了
Oh, awkward for me.
加油赶超我吧 林戈
Good luck following that, Ringo.
这是你们的电线
I believe this belongs to you.
我也不想拖着一房子在后面跑
I don't want to drag the house along with me.
小猴子们 都过来
Come here, you little monkeys.
再见 爷爷 我们会想你的
Bye, Grandpa. We'll miss you.
真希望能把你们一起带走
I wish I could take you with me.
-路上小心 爷爷 -我尽量
- Drive safe, Grandpa. - Oh, I'll try.
你真的不留下吃早餐吗
You sure you don't want to stay for breakfast?
不 我该上路了
No, I ought to be hitting the road.
再会了
Well, adios.
爸 等一下
Dad, hold on.
-我能和你谈谈吗 -好呀
- Can I talk to you for a second? - Sure.
宝贝们 我们走吧
Guys. Come on.
我觉得你没跟我说实话
I don't think you're being honest with me.
我知道你有什么事在心上
I- I know something is going on with you.
到底是什么事
What's up?
心上 我的内裤倒是提得太上面了
Something up? Well, my boxers are, uh, riding a little high.
我没在没心气跟你开玩笑
I'm not in the mood for jokes right now,
-虽然刚才那句逗死了 -谢谢
- although you nailed that. - Thanks.
-说得真好 -谢了
- Great stuff. - Thanks.
-我没事 -没事吗
- It's nothing. - Oh, it's nothing?
-不是跟妈有关吧 -不是
- Nothing to do with Mom? - No!
好吧 其实有关 我坠入爱河了
Well, yeah. I've fallen in love.
我的天
Oh, my God.
-她是谁 -是他
- Who is she? - He!
什么
What?
就是那边的小家伙啊
It's that little guy right over there.
快过来 过来 过来
Come on over here. Come on. Come on.
好孩子 瞧瞧他
There you go. Ah, look at him.
在驾车穿越全国的路上
Driving across country,
这个小崽子成功地
this little bastard nuzzled his way
夺走了我的心 对不对
right into my heart, didn't ya?
所以你就是不想送掉这狗罢了
So this is just about you not wanting to leave the dog?
你该和妈说清楚
Well, you should tell Mom.
和它在路上的这三天
Those three days on the road with him
是我人生最快乐的日子
were the happiest of my life.
这话你就别对她说了
You should leave that part out.
我不想因为留下斯科特而让爷爷难过
I don't want to keep Scout if it makes Grandpa sad.
我知道 宝贝 可是奶奶会过敏
Yeah, I know, sweetie. But Grandma has allergies,
所以斯科特必须留下
so Scout has to stay with us.
她可以打抗过敏针嘛
Well, she could always just get some allergy shots.
亲爱的 你不会愿意让她遭那罪的
Honey, you don't want to put her through that.
靠 当年我还为她做了结扎手术呢
Hell, back in the day, I got a vasectomy for her.
爸 爸 真的
Dad. Dad. Please.
斯科特是你的狗
Scout's- Scout's your dog.
他应该跟着你走
He should go with you.
那好吧 这可是你逼我的
Okay, you twisted my arm.
谢了 儿子 多谢你看穿了我的伪装
Thanks, Son. Thanks for poking through the armor.
-您下面也快穿出来了 -什么
- You're poking through the armor down there. - What?
骗到你了
Made you look.
你真是块奇才
You are a treasure.
来吧 斯科特 我们走了
Come on, Scout. Let's mosey.
等一下
Oh, oh, oh! Oh, wait.
-他喜欢这个 -那是肯定的
- He loves that, yeah. - Oh, I bet he does.
不 斯科特 这次轮到我开车了
No, Scout. This time I drive.
好好笑
You still got it!
真不敢相信我会这么说
I can't believe I'm saying this,
不过我好像和我爸更加亲近了
but I think I might have actually gotten even closer with my dad.
真不敢相信他把我的狗带走了
I can't believe he took my dog.
-再见 -爷爷再见 爱你哦
- Bye-bye. - Bye, Grandpa! Love you!
再见 老爸
Bye, Dad.
-爷爷再见 我爱你 -卢克 停下
- Bye, Grandpa! I love you! - Luke, stay!
-卢克 停下 -下次再来 再见啦
-Luke, stay! - Come back soon! I'll see you later!
卢克 停下
Luke, stay!
-卢克 -停下
- Luke! - Stay!
弗兰克
Frank.
杰 真高兴见到你
Hey, Jay. Good to see you.
我也是 没想到你会在这儿
Great to see you. Didn't expect to find you here.
当我孙女男友的乐队
Well, listen, when my granddaughter's boyfriend's band
和我儿媳妇弟弟的男友
plays an under-21 club with my daughter-in-law's
在少年俱乐部一起演出 我不会错过
brother's gay partner, I show up.
这可是礼节问题
That's just how I was raised.
-你还没见过我太太吧 歌洛莉亚 -你好
- I don't think you met my wife, Gloria. - Hola.
很高兴见到你 你真是漂亮啊
Oh, it's a pleasure. You are a lovely woman.
-你一定是弗兰克吧 -哎呀呀
- You must be Frank. - Okay, then,
你比国庆节时的拉斯维加斯街头还要火热啊
you are hotter than a Las Vegas sidewalk on the Fourth of July.
-我太过火了吗 -不 没事 弗兰克
- Did I go too far? - Not you, Frank. No.